[{"answer": "President Obama has decided to attack success.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 2, "question": "Who's got the real answer to fixing the economy?", "qSentId": 1}, {"answer": "Great, it's great to be here.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Maybe not, maybe 20 percent that they say haven't worked out.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Has he always done the right thing for those companies?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "I'm disputing for a moment your integrity.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "When am I not honest?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I think making the job creation argument was not the smartest case to make.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "-- it was about job creation?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "If it is, Romney ought to wipe it out.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Do you think this will be the key battleground, the ideological dispute we're now seeing over this?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "This -- plays something from an interview I did with Howard Schultz from Starbucks on this show.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "No, but does it keep jobs, Piers, yes?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Ugly.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "What is your opinion of the whole IPO launch of Facebook this week?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Some people made a mistake.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "How after everything that we've been through in the last few years, could a company make that kind of loss without apparently some of the top people having any idea?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Right up to now, absolutely right.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "How Jamie Dimon dealt with this properly?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Of its own money.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "So if you're -- if you're an average American watching this and they're saying, how can a company lose over $2 billion, maybe $3 billion?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "No, we don't suspect that.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Do you suspect that?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "They were trying to hedge the (INAUDIBLE) slid into something else.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "What do you suspect was going on?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Is he right to do that?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Pretty good, it's not great, it's nowhere near what we need and we're going to grow in the 2 to 2.5 percent range over the next couple of quarters.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Should people be feeling generally more confident?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "A lot better than it was three years ago.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "But a lot better than it was, say, three years ago?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Well, he's done a job of bringing it back in the cycle.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "So Obama has done a pretty good job then?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "No, I don't like what he's done.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Do you give him due credit for that?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "That's a tough one for me.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "What do you give him credit for in terms of the economy?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I was very fortunate.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "That was 1996.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "When was the last time you actually spoke, you two?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "No, no, it wasn't like that.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Can you repeat them?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Who said that, \"I'm done\"?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Well, I've heard a lot of numbers --", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "What is the single biggest offer you have had to put it all behind you and get back on a stage together?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "I'd say, I'd say it starts off with seven figures, yes.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Seven figures, eight figures?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I don't think it's a matter of that, it really isn't.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Is there any check that would tempt you?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Let's take a short break.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "And so I don't think there's a price tag that anybody's going to put in front of us that's going to make that work, you know?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Well, you're talking about a concert that was in -- I think it was in Argentina, back in the '90s, I mentioned in the interview we did before, which was when it was pouring really thick rain and there was steam coming off the audience and we were playing \"November Rain\" and the timing was such that as soon as we went into the cords of \"November Rain\" this rainstorm started and just seeing this crowd sort of bouncing in the rhythm of the song and the --", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "What was the moment for you?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "The physical experience is there's the energy of the band playing a very heartfelt song, you know, and then you have that interaction with an audience that's reacting to that and it's a huge amount of energy.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "And for someone like me who's never going to come close to that, what is the -- what is the physical experience?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Yes, I feel very connected to my British roots.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Do you feel remotely English?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, some of those people -- well, OK, if you're about people that are living that I've actually played with before, Iggy Pop is great.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "If you were creating a super group, all the talent that you have ever seen, played with, whatever, who would it be?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "That's what I'm trying to figure out.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Who would be your drummer?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "It would be cool to jam with Jack White.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "No one wants to do this, but who would play the other guitarist to you?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, that was really sweet, but he's a really great guy.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What did you think of what he said?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Almost seven.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Slash, you, basically, you're a rock star and I have discussed it with you before, but for the benefit of this interview, I just want to -- you've been clean, what, six years now?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Being able to look at it from both sides, not being so out of it that I couldn't get some sort of a perspective on it.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "What was the thing that got you out of it, personally?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "You chose to end up hiring a number of hotel rooms in the same hotel, for various women, none of who knew about each other?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "It was a little bit expensive.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Expensive, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Yeah, definitely.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Do you feel like you have met your match with her?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "When she and I first met, I knew that I was hooked when we first met and I tried to keep my distance from her for a long time because I knew once that relationship was seriously established, things were going to change.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Is that what you needed to do?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I would say properly, that was the first time.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "How many timings would you say in your life you have been properly in love?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "I really try.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "ORGAN: Are you good dad?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "I don't have like an unachieved dream.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Do you have one?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Yes, of course, it was a great honor.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Was it for you a great honor to be inducted into the hall of fame?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "I didn't even really read it.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Did you understand where Axl was coming from with his protests about it all?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "A template for your life.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "You think?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Muslim.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Oh, Muslim?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Well, I and some of my editors have worked on a lot of these books, too, but they're very, very good books.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "You've written 77 books?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Well, who knows.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Are you related to him?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "We are all American.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Isn't that the point of America, that none of you are?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "If I were thinking about food at that point ...", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "What's the last thing you would want to eat?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "If I was very hungry and I was told that I only had an hour?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Probably good, fresh eggs.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "What would you start with?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "That's my main course.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "And the main course, what would you have?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Britain.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Well, again, where do you think that came from, fish and chips?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Well, they're somewhere in the book.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Where are the mushy peas?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Yes, they're okay.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Do you like mushy peas?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "No, no, no, no.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Right out of the can, right?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "But you would seriously just have eggs as your last meal?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Or maybe a couple of bottles, if I knew I was going ...", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "American or French?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "It depends.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "You wouldn't have American wine, would you?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "I love white burgundy.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "ORGAN: Wouldn't you go for a nice burgundy?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "The pies.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Of all these dishes in here, which are the ones that you were most excited, would you say?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "I think pies are so typically American.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Why pies?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "Cobblers.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Pardon?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "It can be or they can be a derogatory term.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "Cobblers are for shoes?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Yes, I will.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "I love lemon meringue.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Apple, cherry, plum, what do you like?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "You still enjoy cooking?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Something I sort of created.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "What's the Martha Wrap?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "Tell me what it is.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "Can I plug it?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "I'm a careful griller.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "Are you a big griller?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "Well, there's a lot of secrets.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "What's the secret to a good barbecue?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "OK, a hot, hot fire.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "What bit of advice would you give me?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "Not like completely black coated, but a little dash of black.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Burned?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Do you press your hamburgers on the grill?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "Yes, I like them all sort of compacted and blackened.", "docId": "120523pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "You compact them?", "qSentId": 691}]